[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 28]
Yao, do it.
Kill him.
Do it!
Kill him!
-Wake up.
Gu Yu.
Where is your prince?
His Majesty has suffered a relapse,
so His Highness has gone to the palace.
He went to the palace?
Dead?
Suige is dead?
Suige is dead...
Suige is dead.
Yao.
Come on, get up.
Suige...
Yao.
Suige is dead.
Look at me!
Look at me.
Father.
I've failed you.
It's my fault.
You shouldn't have helped me.
In this world,
I can turn my back on everything—
everything except you.
I'm not a good son.
I'm the one who dragged you down.
You've been a loyal subject
your entire life,
yet because of me,
you've become a traitor.
It's me. I've pushed you into
this desperate situation.
I've ruined everything for you,
Father!
For you,
I can give up everything.
Traitor
or
rebel—
let them call me whatever they will.
As long as I can save your life,
I'll accept whatever comes,
no matter the cost!
Pull yourself together!
I'll pin the crimes
of patricide and regicide
on Feng Suige,
and you'll be
the hero who killed him.
Do you understand?
Stand up.
Stand up!
Pull yourself together!
Do you know that
right now, if anyone suspects
the true cause of Feng Suige's death,
it will very likely
trigger a mutiny in the Feng Battalion?
So,
you must stay clear-headed.
We must properly
dispose of Feng Suige's body.
Do you hear me?
Alright.
Father, don't worry.
The route out of the palace
has been arranged.
The Imperial Guards on duty along the way
are all my men.
I'll find a secluded spot
and bury Suige there.
Good, good boy.
I have prepared a carriage.
Take Feng Suige's body
out of the palace.
My token will
allow you to pass through every gate
without obstruction.
Marquis Murong, is it done?
Please rest assured, Your Majesty.
I've instructed Yao.
He'll change clothes
as soon as he leaves the palace.
Your Majesty will not be implicated.
Now that...
both father and son are dead,
has Your Majesty decided
how to announce this to the world?
Feng Suige attempted to usurp the throne,
committed regicide, and fled.
And Yao
executed the traitor Feng Suige,
avenging His Majesty.
Years ago, I
helped Feng Pingcheng
ascend to the throne.
I was a founding subject of the dynasty.
Now...
I've cleared the way for Your Majesty
and supported the Second Prince's
ascension to the throne.
This credit
should go to Yao.
Rest assured, Marquis Murong.
When Chengyang ascends the throne,
Yao will be a founding subject.
He will surely rise to
the highest position in the court.
From now on,
our Zhuang family and your Murong family
will be bound together,
sharing weal and woe.
My deepest gratitude...
Your Majesty the Empress Dowager.
Marquis Murong, I'll never forget
your great kindness.
My father's spirit
can finally rest in peace.
Feng Pingcheng's illness
has flared up again?
News came from the palace,
and Feng Suige went to the palace
early this morning.
I don't know what's wrong,
but I can't shake
this uneasy feeling.
You're just worrying too much.
What could possibly happen?
But Feng Pingcheng's health
has been failing for a long time.
It's likely he won't make it.
If Feng Pingcheng
truly doesn't make it this time,
then Suige is just accompanying his father
on his final journey.
But you've come at the right time.
These patients need attention—
some need their bandages changed,
and others need their medicine prepared.
I'm short-handed here,
so stay and help.
All right.
My Lord.
It's Feng Suige.
You always said
a man's duty was to serve his country
on the battlefield.
Even if one day we fall in battle,
we'll have no regrets.
I used to scold you
for speaking of ill omens.
I never thought
I'd be the one burying you.
[Zhengnian Hall]
Miss Yixiao!
Ruyan?
Why are you here?
S-Something bad has happened.
What happened?
It's Feng Suige.
[Zhengnian Hall]
About five li southeast of here,
there's a forest.
About 100 paces into the woods,
I left a pearl hairpin.
Feng Suige should be somewhere nearby.
That's impossible.
It can't be.
No, it can't be.
♪ The rain drifts endlessly ♪
He'll be fine!
♪ The old dream burns the heart ♪
♪ Dreams sink into ruin ♪
He'll be fine.
♪ Missing the warmth of your palm ♪
He must be fine.
♪ Awaiting dusk ♪
♪ Shadows take root in the mountain pass ♪
♪ In just a moment, tears stained ♪
♪ Amid the bustling sound
of wind and rain ♪
♪ Who laughs at me,
heart cold as the desert? ♪
♪ Dreams turn through a lifetime ♪
♪ Who sighs for me,
enduring separations? ♪
♪ Love is a trial, harsh and cold ♪
Feng Suige.
♪ Who crushes the lingering pain for me? ♪
♪ Clouds vanish, rain ceases, seek me ♪
Feng Suige!
♪ The world is vast and far ♪
♪ Time is unbearable to endure ♪
♪ Lost in the wilderness ♪
♪ I've been looking for you ♪
♪ Even if devastation fills my eyes ♪
♪ The shadows continue to sway ♪
I'm here.
I'm here to save you.
♪ The phoenix going against light ♪
I'm here to save you!
♪ Has been looking for a thousand miles ♪
♪ As years pass, dust stirs,
stirring deep longing ♪
♪ All I ask is to be together forever ♪
[Closed]
[Zhengnian Hall]
His external wound isn't fatal.
His pupils are dilated,
and his pulse is weak.
He's unconscious
because his airway is obstructed.
Fortunately, his strong willpower
and survival instinct
have kept him barely alive.
And you found him just in time
and saved him,
helping him
cling to life.
However, his heart is failing.
I can't guarantee I can save him.
I've already sent Jie
with the Imperial Guards
to surround Feng Suige's residence
and wipe out his men.
Once
we eliminate all of
Feng Suige's trusted followers,
his Feng Battalion will be leaderless
and won't be able to cause
any trouble anymore.
Yao.
Since things have come to this,
don't dwell on it.
Father,
you must be
very disappointed
to have such a worthless son
who has ruined everything for you.
Yao,
stand up right now.
Yao.
Remember this:
from now on, our Murong family
depends on you.
You must not lose your spirit.
Alright,
Father.
Uncle.
Feng Suige's residence is empty.
His trusted followers are
nowhere to be found.
Our scouts report
that they went to Zhengnian Hall.
Zhengnian Hall?
That's a place for healing the sick.
As far as I know,
Fu Yixiao often goes there.
Yes.
Zhengnian Hall is
located in a busy market area.
I dare not lead troops there recklessly,
fearing the palace coup might be exposed
and ruin your plans.
Please make the decision, Uncle.
The news of Feng Suige's death
hasn't spread yet.
They shouldn't be aware.
Yao,
when you buried his body,
you weren't discovered by anyone,
were you?
I personally led the people to bury him.
There's no way the news could've leaked.
Looks like now...
we can't worry about too much now.
Jie,
take the Imperial Guards
and surround Zhengnian Hall.
No one associated with Feng Suige
shall be spared!
Kill them all!
Yes, Uncle.
How is he?
Please say something.
How is he doing exactly?
Not well.
I've restored his pulse,
so he's still alive.
But I can't say
whether he'll survive.
What should we do?
His yin and yang energies are in chaos,
and his qi and blood flow is blocked—
his life hangs by a thread.
At this point,
I can only take a risky approach:
use potent medicine to stimulate his heart
and buy him a few more days.
But to truly save him,
we must get him to the Storm Alliance!
Storm Alliance?
The place where Ning Fei was saved?
That's right.
There's no time to waste.
Let's depart immediately.
Once we start, there's no turning back.
I'll go prepare the medicine now.
My medicine can only
sustain him for five days.
If we can't get him
to the Storm Alliance within five days
to receive treatment...
it will truly be too late.
Even if it costs me my life,
I'll keep him alive.
Alright.
How is His Highness?
Quick, go prepare a carriage.
I'll explain everything on the way.
Okay.
Let's go.
Thank you.
I'll never forget
this favor.
You're welcome.
You saved my life.
I'm really glad I could help.
From now on,
I'll stay in Yujing City
and find an opportunity
to deal with Murong Yao.
If you need anything,
call on me anytime.
Okay.
Take care of yourself
and be careful.
Mother...
Are you saying my brother...
my brother killed Grandfather,
and he also killed Father?
Yes.
Why would he do that?
Chengyang,
some things
you will understand naturally in time.
After your grandfather died,
your father intended to pass
the throne to you.
But your brother wouldn't allow it.
All because of the throne?
I never even thought
about fighting him for the throne.
Why didn't he just ask me?
Why?
Why would I fight him for it?
I wouldn't fight him for anything!
Because he never truly saw you
as his brother.
You are half-brothers.
In his heart,
his only flesh and blood
was Feng Xiyang.
Naturally, he'd see you as a threat.
I just never expected
he'd be so ruthless
as to kill your father
and usurp the throne.
Chengyang,
you were your father's favorite son
and also the one
your grandfather cared about most.
You must remember their teachings
and become a wise ruler.
Chengyang,
no matter who else falls now,
you cannot fall.
Now it falls to you
to hold Susha together.
[Zhengnian Hall]
General.
Speak.
No one from the Feng household is inside.
[Murong Jie, General of the Jinwu Guard]
We just caught some patients.
They said a group of people
escorted a carriage away.
That must be them.
When did they leave?
Not long ago.
After them!
Yes!
Report!
There are Imperial Guards behind us!
Looks like they're coming for us!
Qiongqi Unit,
follow me back!
I'll help!
-Yes, sir!
Lu Ke!
Hurry!
Stop them!
There are pursuers!
This is bad.
There are too many pursuers.
Gu Yu and Hound
can't hold them off at all!
Guys,
follow me back to cover the retreat!
-Yes, sir!
-Lu Ke!
Protect His Highness and go!
Let's go!
Move aside!
Hound!
Don't waste time on them!
Follow me in pursuit!
Murong Jie!
Honor heaven above,
respect the earth below!
Be loyal to the ruler and the kingdom,
and never fail the people!
Stop...
Your Highness...
Hound!
Gu Yu!
Brother!
Kill them all!
-Kill them!
Brother!
Leave me be.
Brother.
General,
we couldn't catch up to that carriage.
We lost them.
I know you're worried
about your father's condition.
If you really want to return to Susha,
I can help you.
When I was taken away
like a criminal,
you did nothing.
Now you come saying you want to help me?
I'll find a way to make Xia Jingyan
let you go back.
Even if...
I have to bow my head and beg him.
For my sake, you're willing
to put aside your pride
and beg your greatest enemy.
Should I be
eternally grateful for that?
I know you resent me,
but we both know
that on your own,
you cannot leave Jinxiu.
No.
I don't resent you.
You can only resent someone
you care about.
I no longer feel
anything for you.
So how could I resent you?
If that's the case...
then I'll return your freedom.
[Letter of Divorce]
All this talk about letting me go
or returning my freedom—
you think I don't understand?
You're just trying
to use this chance
to pay me back
for helping you escape Susha.
So you can feel better about yourself,
thinking you owe me nothing.
How can there be a person as hypocritical
and heartless as you?
Now that things have come to this,
what's the point of saying all this?
You and I
were never meant to be.
"Never meant to be"?
When you were trapped in Susha,
why didn't you say that?
When you had nowhere to turn,
Now that I'm no longer useful to you,
you say we were never meant to be?
Xia Jingshi,
you disgust me.
I don't need your help.
Stop this pretense.
Xia Jingshi, hear this:
you're merely
a useless prince consort of Susha.
What right do you have
to cast me aside with a letter of divorce?
It is I, Feng Xiyang,
who will cast you aside!
From today on,
we have nothing to do with each other.
Our bond as husband and wife
is severed once and for all!
Then, Princess, as you wish.
From this moment on,
we have no connection whatsoever.
From now on, whatever I do
is none of your concern.
Princess Xiyang,
farewell.
Stop.
I know you hold a grudge
against my brother.
I don't care what else you do.
But remember this:
if you dare to harm my brother,
I'll kill you with my own hands.
What did you say?
The body's gone?
Yes.
I was worried, so I went to check myself.
The body has been taken away.
Father,
could Feng Suige
still be alive?
Jie,
how did it go?
Jie...
Uncle,
please forgive my incompetence.
I failed to kill all of Feng Suige's
subordinates.
They fought desperately
and escorted a carriage away.
A carriage?
Where did they flee to?
To the Susha border.
However, there are
many intersections there.
Based on the wheel tracks alone,
we can't tell
which way they fled.
However, I've already
sent men to pursue them
along different routes.
Well done.
Jie,
you should go back
and rest now.
Feng Suige
has to be in that carriage.
But if
it were just his corpse,
there'd be no need for them
to fight so desperately to protect it.
Could...
Feng Suige truly still be alive?
Whether he lives or dies,
his defeat is sealed.
Even if he still draws breath,
he must be severely injured.
Before long,
Feng Chengyang will ascend the throne.
By then,
it will be a done deal.
In this game,
Feng Suige has already lost.
Father,
I was incompetent.
If Feng Suige truly is still alive,
I'll kill him with my own hands!
Yao.
No matter what,
you must remember this:
publicly, we must claim
that Feng Suige is dead
and that you
personally executed him.
This way,
when Feng Chengyang ascends the throne,
you'll receive the greatest credit.
By then,
once we control the situation,
even if there are unexpected changes,
they won't be cause for concern.
I understand, Father.
Alright.
You should go back and rest as well.
Let me think about
how to inform the Empress Dowager.
Your Majesty,
over the past few days,
the Prince of Zhennan
has either remained in Rongyang Palace
or wandered around the grounds.
He hasn't done anything suspicious.
Over these past few days, I
deliberately removed the guards
from Rongyang Palace,
hoping he would reveal
his true intentions.
But he's made no move at all.
Why do you think that is?
This servant is too foolish
to fathom the reason.
Tell me...
could Xia Jingshi
have planted moles
around me?
Your Majesty,
shall I investigate?
Everyone around me
has been thoroughly vetted.
Xia Jingshi's reach
can't extend that far.
Is it possible
that Xia Jingshi has guessed
Your Majesty's intentions?
That is possible.
But what if he has?
I'll kill him sooner or later.
Your Majesty,
urgent news from Susha!
Susha's Prime Minister Zhuang Shen
has died.
The First Prince Feng Suige...
committed regicide to usurp the throne?
Feng Pingcheng is dead.
Feng Suige was executed?
Your Majesty.
It's destiny.
I truly am blessed by heaven.
I was just thinking about
how to eliminate Xia Jingshi.
And heaven has given me this opportunity.
The Empress Dowager has arrived!
All of you, leave.
Mother.
Mother, you've heard, haven't you?
Feng Pingcheng and Feng Suige
are both dead.
What a pleasant surprise!
The one who will
succeed to the throne in Susha
can only be the Second Prince,
Feng Chengyang.
A young ruler will bring
uncertainty to the nation.
Prime Minister Zhuang is also dead.
Susha's court will surely be in chaos.
In that case,
Susha will be too preoccupied
with its own affairs.
Perhaps for the next 10 or even 20 years,
they won't dare
wage war against our Jinxiu again.
Right, Mother?
What are you trying to say?
Then...
Then does that mean
we no longer need to
keep Xia Jingshi alive?
I'm warning you,
don't act rashly.
Why?
You said it yourself!
You said we needed to spare his life
to make use of him!
He's of no use now,
so why can't I kill him?
Why can't I kill him?
Whether Xia Jingshi has value
is not determined by Susha.
It's determined by you!
As the ruler of a nation,
how can you be so foolish?
In the end,
you just can't bear to kill him.
Don't treat court politics
as child's play!
Xia Jingshi's value isn't
just in helping us against Susha.
The Zhennan Army under his command
is his greatest value!
Without my order,
do not move against him.
Do you understand?
[Edict of Condemnation]
The criminal Feng Suige
committed patricide and regicide.
Such heinous crimes against all order
are condemned by both gods and men!
Now, struck by heaven's wrath,
he has been executed,
his body left to rot in the wilderness!
By imperial decree:
strip him of all titles,
and remove his name from
the imperial family records as a traitor!
All his family assets
shall be confiscated.
His household servants shall be exiled
for military service,
with no pardon for 30 years!
Lord Ling,
where on earth are you taking us?
We've been walking for ages
and haven't seen a soul.
Can the Storm Alliance
really be in these mountains?
Carry him properly
and stop talking nonsense.
Remember, once we enter the alliance,
don't mention the Feng family—
especially not the First Prince!
Why?
Lord Ling,
what exactly is the Storm Alliance?
What kind of people are there?
They're all
refugees and wounded soldiers.
Speaking of which—
before we enter the alliance,
let me give you a warning.
The alliance recognizes
no national boundaries.
It has only four branches: Fishing,
Woodcutting, Farming, and Studying.
Each branch has an elder.
Any matter
is decided
by discussion among the four elders.
So watch what you say,
or they might decide to get rid of us.
Y-Y-You're
making it sound so creepy.
Why does this alliance
make me so uneasy?
-Can we really go there?
-Let me tell you something
even more unsettling.
If you can't remember
what I just told you,
the person you're carrying
may die at any moment.
Go!
I'll remember that!