[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 31]
Zhuang Shen attempted to
have Feng Suige assassinated
in the street,
which ended in failure.
Feng Suige then broke into
the Zhuang Residence,
captured Zhuang Shen,
and took him to the imperial palace.
Zhuang Shen could be said
as a relative of yours, right?
My brother once told me
Zhuang Shen was responsible
for our mother's death.
That explains the enmity.
Feng Suige killed Zhuang Shen
in the Susha imperial palace,
in the presence of all.
Then, the Zhuang family's property
was ordered to be confiscated.
A powerful official was convicted
of treason within just one day.
Your brother was said to be
decisive and resolute.
Indeed, how crafty of him.
The next morning,
Feng Suige slayed the Emperor
alone with a sword,
planning to usurp the throne.
Give it to me! I'll read it myself!
Feng Suige's atrocity
was finally revealed.
Murong Zhong and Murong Yao
executed him in the end.
Are the investigators
you sent out for this matter
reliable?
What?
You still don't believe it?
Murong Yao
was my brother's best friend.
Murong Zhong
was like an uncle to us,
as he watched us grow up.
My brother was even closer to him
than to our father!
How could they have
possibly killed my brother?
Are there raging flames of fury
in your heart now,
amidst the confusion
about who you should hate
and who you should direct your anger to?
I said it right, didn't I?
Oh, you.
How foolish!
Why not just vent out
the anger in your heart?
Since you have no idea
who you should take revenge on,
just kill whoever you want!
If you kill the wrong person, so be it.
It's better than restraining yourself,
isn it?
Can you find out
who my enemy really is?
One more investigation?
Isn't everything
written clearly in this report?
It was Murong Zhong and his son
who killed your father and brother.
What more evidence do you need?
Why care about if there are hidden truths?
All will be over when I kill them for you!
Your father already died.
So did your brother.
[Feng Suige's atrocity
was finally revealed]
[Murong Zhong and Murong Yao
executed him in the end]
They were killed
by Murong Zhong and his son.
See for yourself!
That's the spirit.
I'm telling you, from now on,
I disallow you to restrain yourself again.
Life is about
doing whatever you want.
Curse whoever you want!
Kill whoever you want!
That's the way to please yourself!
Get out!
Get out of here!
-Feng Xiyang!
-Get out!
Scram!
Feng Xiyang, you...
You...
Have some more
snacks and cakes delivered
to Prince Xiyang.
Make them look pretty.
That might cheer her up.
What are you waiting for?
Go get it done!
Yes.
Our biggest concern
has become reality.
His eyes are cured
with Lady An's treatment,
indicating that the blood clots
in his brain have resolved.
That's good news.
I thought the worst scenario would be
he losing all the memories,
but the real situation
is unexpectedly worse.
He does remember some things.
But he thinks of you as an enemy,
forgetting all the good things about you.
Is it possible
to help him recover all the memories?
You heard what Lady An said, didn't you?
The brain
is incredibly intricate.
No one can tell if he can
recollect all the memories.
Enough.
Let's not leave it to fate.
Miss Yixiao,
don't worry too much.
When His Highness wakes up,
I'll tell him everything,
even if I have to pin him down.
Great. That's a good idea.
See,
you know best about their story.
Yeah.
Telling it to him in detail
will help to jog his memory.
Exactly!
Kiddo,
Lu Ke is right.
Just don't worry.
Suige's mind is a mess now.
Whatever he says or does,
don't take it to heart.
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I'm mentally prepared.
At least,
his life has been saved.
he can see now.
At least,
unlike me in the past,
he still knows who he is.
Alright.
Say no more.
I'll go talk to Lady An.
I'll beg her to work out a plan.
I heard
Feng Suige had come to.
He did wake up from a coma,
but his condition is complex.
I'll go find Lady An.
Today, I'm here
to deliver you a message.
I've made some inquiries.
Rumor has it in Yujing City
that Feng Suige killed the Emperor
and was then executed by the Murong family
in the name of defending the sovereignty.
That is to say,
nobody but us knows
Feng Suige is still alive.
The Second Prince of Susha
has already ascended the throne.
[In Storm Alliance on Wufeng Mountain]
Your Highness,
you finally woke up!
I meant it when I said I could wake him up
by putting a needle in only one acupoint.
Impressive.
How are you feeling?
Do you remember who I am?
What about him?
You're Lord Ling.
He is Lu Ke.
Terrific.
What's going on with me?
Where am I?
I can't explain to you
the whole thing right now.
Just remember this:
you escaped death not long ago.
You need a good rest now.
Don't ask any questions.
Lu Ke,
have we conquered Pingling City yet?
What?
Please try thinking of a way
to help him recover
more memories.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Try figuring out a way, please.
Yeah.
But I...
Fu Yixiao...
I'm going to kill you!
No, no!
Calm down.
Calm down, Your Highness.
-Listen to me...
-You have to leave now!
You need a good rest now.
Get some rest!
See?
Calm down.
Are you alright, Your Highness?
Take a breath.
Stay calm.
Let's go.
Move it!
I know you're hurting inside.
If you're really that upset,
cry it out.
It'll make you feel better.
How can anyone take this?
A once
loving couple
has become
mortal enemies.
You're saying
she's my dearest and beloved one?
How is that possible?
Your Highness,
why would I ever lie to you?
She really is. You've just forgotten that.
Due to severe physical trauma
and prolonged suffocation,
there were blood clots in your brain,
which caused you blindness.
Lady An made the clots go away
and fixed your eyes
with the Golden Acupuncture.
But meanwhile,
you lost some memories,
and your mind was disturbed.
That's why when you saw Fu Yixiao,
you behaved
completely different than usual,
and felt irritable, agitated,
and out of control.
Then how do you explain this scar?
When she shot an arrow at me,
she clearly meant to kill me!
This is an attack
I will never forget.
That arrow attack
is the most indelible memory in his mind?
Exactly.
I guess that's the reason.
He can't remember
what happened
after the Battle of Pingling,
when you shot that arrow
at him.
Nonetheless,
perhaps this is destiny.
If it weren't for this arrow
that changed you two's lives,
he might've
forgotten everything by now,
and the situation would've become worse.
If he had lost all the memories,
it would be even harder
for him to recover them.
I've seen
many similar cases.
He'd be too stubborn
to take anyone's advice
or to trust anyone.
How can you even not
believe my words?
How am I supposed to believe all of this?
If it's really as you say—
that I've lost memories,
then what should I do
to get them back?
You must leave him.
All you can do now
is leave him.
You have to disappear from his life,
and to never see him again.
Don't show your face either.
Just let him gradually forget you.
Give him time
for a full recovery.
Can you do that?
Well...
How long do I need to wait?
Three or five years.
Maybe a decade.
It could also be a lifetime.
There's nothing
we can say to convince you now.
Forget it.
We can't rush anything.
Listen,
just focus on recuperating.
When you recover,
we'll resume the discussion.
I want to meet with Fu Yixiao.
What?
Why meet with her?
Do you still want to kill her?
I want to know the truth.
Fine. The truth is as follows.
In order to save your life,
Fu Yixiao gathered us
and went to a lot of trouble
in the past many days.
I'm telling you,
only when you recall who she really is
can you go meet her.
Otherwise, just don't see her again.
If it takes you a lifetime
to figure it out,
then stay away from her for a lifetime!
How long do you mean
by "a lifetime"?
Don't you understand?
Sometimes it's better not to see
or have feelings for someone.
Your affection for him
is like a sword.
The closer you are to him,
the deeper the sword sticks into him.
When your wishes are all fulfilled,
he'll be covered in wounds.
But if I leave him...
You'll feel physically
and emotionally hurt,
while he'll be safe and sound.
Emperor.
What are you doing?
Picking flowers.
Can't you see that, Mother?
Picking flowers?
What else can I do?
The weather is nice today.
Can't I take a walk outside?
Aren't you out here too, Mother?
You could've asked others
to pick the flowers you liked.
How can you do it yourself?
Mother,
it never occurred to me
until this very day
that some flowers
must be picked by myself,
or there wouldn't be fun.
Some flowers may look gorgeous,
but they wither quickly.
When that happens,
their colors will fade,
leaving only poisonous thorns behind.
It hurts to be pricked.
I've long grown accustomed
to thornless flowers.
It feels nice...
to be pricked.
I've warned you
not to go rogue
or to hit on Feng Xiyang.
Go rogue?
It's true that you're my mother,
but I am the Emperor!
I know exactly what I'm doing.
You grew with the tree,
sharing the same roots.
But eventually,
you would detach from the tree.
As it thrives and flourishes,
you would travel far away.
Perhaps
this is the fate
I can't escape either.
All you can do now
is leave him.
You have to disappear from his life,
and to never see him again.
♪ The rain drifts endlessly ♪
Don't show your face either.
♪ The old dream burns the heart ♪
Just let him gradually forget you.
♪ Dreams sink into ruin ♪
Give him time for a full recovery.
Can you do that?
♪ Missing the warmth of your palm ♪
♪ Awaiting dusk ♪
♪ Shadows take root in the mountain pass ♪
Can you make me a promise?
If I ever forget you,
♪ In just a moment, tears stained ♪
be mad at me, beat me,
and yell at me as you like.
But please don't be disappointed in me.
♪ Amid the bustling sound
of wind and rain ♪
And definitely don't leave me
♪ Who laughs at me,
heart cold as the desert? ♪
because of disappointment,
will you?
♪ Dreams turn through a lifetime ♪
♪ Who sighs for me,
enduring separations? ♪
♪ Love is a trial, harsh and cold ♪
♪ Who crushes the lingering pain for me? ♪
♪ Clouds vanish, rain ceases, seek me ♪
I've promised
to never leave you.
♪ The world is vast and far ♪
♪ Time is unbearable to endure ♪
Miss Yixiao.
I tried explaining
to His Highness just now,
but he wouldn't listen
and he drove me away.
He's still
quite weak right now.
He has probably fallen asleep.
I'm still worried about him.
Does he recall
what happened to his father?
He can't remember anything that happened
after the Battle of Pingling.
He's forgotten the most painful memories.
I wonder
if it's a blessing in disguise.
Don't worry too much,
Miss Yixiao.
Elder Zhou and Lord Ling
are now considering
if there are better ways
to jog His Highness's memory.
If we're out of options,
I'll spill everything
at the risk of infuriating His Highness.
Don't do that.
He needs to rest now,
since he's weak.
Just tell him
Fu Yixiao has left.
But...
This is the best solution now.
It helps him recuperate.
There's one more option.
Maybe we can give it a try.
Your Highness,
given the poor blood flow in your legs,
you should soak your feet
in warm water more often.
Let me help you!
It's just to bathe your feet.
Why are you acting like a sulky housewife?
It's much more comfortable barefoot.
You should take your shoes off too.
Take them off.
Alright. I can do it myself.
You just fell into the water,
yet you are
acting like a sulking housewife.
Remember to put
plenty of spices on the roast meat.
You like spicy food, don't you?
The spicier, the better.
Besides spicy food,
you also enjoy drinking.
Aside from garlic,
you're not picky at all.
Here you are.
Isn't it too spicy to be put in my mouth?
I'll eat it then.
I see in no one but you
the quality of a wolf,
just like that in myself.
Your Highness,
I want you to have this.
It symbolizes we'll stick together
for the rest of our lives.
This is the first time
I have ever given a gift to a woman.
You cannot refuse it.
have you ever thought about
what kind of man you want to marry?
What's this stuff?
A little wolf.
I'll get Elder Zhou here
to check on you.
What do you need him for?
He can't make wolf figurines.
Your Majesty,
Feng Pingcheng is dead.
The Murong family has yielded real power.
The rule of the new Emperor of Susha
is yet to be consolidated.
Besides,
with Feng Suige's death,
the Susha Army has been left leaderless.
I suggest we send troops
straight to Yujing now.
Your Majesty,
at present,
Jinxiu has a marriage alliance with Susha.
The Princess of Susha
is still in Shengjing.
If we declare war on them now,
all our previous efforts,
including
the Prince of Zhennan's marriage,
will be in vain.
Please reconsider, Your Majesty.
What now?
Since when do you take interest in
major affairs concerning the state
and the military,
Minister of Imperial Stables?
Now that Her Majesty has summoned
us officials for consultations,
I have no reason to hold back my opinions.
What's more, if you are to start a war,
won't you need the assistance
of the Imperial Stables?
Stop bickering.
Wang Encheng,
answer me.
What strategy
do you have in mind for conquering Susha?
Your Majesty,
Jinxiu and Susha
have been fighting each other for years.
Our troops are well-trained
with sufficient supplies.
So, it's not hard
to mobilize the entire army.
There is also a general
standing ready for a war—
the Prince of Zhennan.
All that talking just proves
you're trying to
have the Prince of Zhennan
relocated to Pingling again!
The Prince of Zhennan spent many years
stationing at Pingling
and defending Jinxiu's borders.
What's wrong with recommending
His Highness lead the troops?
Your Majesty,
the Prince of Zhennan was appointed
to marry the Princess of Susha,
but he fled and came back
without permission.
This matter hasn't been settled yet.
If he is designated as the commander,
I'm afraid
people won't accept his authority.
You're only doing this
to give everyone a hard time!
This is pure slander!
Enough!
No more squabbling.
Attacking Susha
is a serious issue.
Let's discuss it another day.
Yes.
You may leave.
All these political disputes
can't be easily settled.
The Emperor and I
don't see eye to eye now.
The most urgent task
is to gain control of Xia Jingshi.
His help is needed to stabilize the court.
God knows when that old punk
Wang Encheng latched onto
the Prince of Zhennan.
He tried to persuade the Empress Dowager
to let the prince return to Pingling
and lead troops against Susha.
Where is Bai Shouzhuo?
Where is he?
You dare not look at me.
Why?
This humble servant dares not offend
the Princess of Zhennan.
What Princess of Zhennan?
Princess Xiyang and the Prince of Zhennan
have broken off their engagement.
From now on,
those who dare to
call her Princess of Zhennan
again
will be heavily punished by me!
As
Your Majesty commands.
Alright.
Stop being angry.
Come with me.
I picked some flowers for you.
Take a look.
See if there's any you like.
I like this one.
This one?
This one's no good.
T-Those are better.
You don't like them?
Put it in my hair.
Get out!
Everyone out!
How odd it is.
This flower
is clearly withered and worn,
yet when placed in your hair,
it looks prettier
than anything I've ever seen.
Were you talking about attacking Susha?
Are you worried about Susha
or Xia Jingshi?
Listen up,
there's no way
I'll let him
out of my sight.
I only care about Susha.
Have you really decided to attack Susha?
Princess of Susha,
you're getting
bolder and bolder.
Pour me a drink.
I can never stay mad at you.
No matter what you do,
as long as I see you,
I'd feel much more cheerful.
Tell me.
What do you want?
Who will lead the Jinxiu army
to attack Susha?
Will it be Xia Jingshi?
He'd love that to happen.
He has colluded with a bunch of officials
and made them lobby the Empress Dowager.
Does he think
I don't know he's behind all that?
I won't give him the satisfaction.
He lives in Rongyang Palace.
How did he get in contact
with those officials?
Settle down.
Clear your mind.
Do as I say.
Relax.
Breathe.
Relax...
Breathe...
This voice...
Why does it sound so familiar?
Greetings, Mother.
Take a seat.
This apricot soup
was freshly made today.
Try some.
Ever since I was little, I've always
remembered you like apricot soup, Mother.
What a good son you are,
for remembering such a tiny detail.
What happened, Mother?
Who has upset you?
It's been a long time
since you married the Princess of Susha.
Mother,
she and I have never
consummated our marriage.
Now,
we're not even husband and wife in name.
Everything that happens
in this palace is no secret to me.
I refrain from saying
certain things
so as to preserve your dignity.
But I'm perfectly aware
that it must make you feel uncomfortable
when she gets closer to the Emperor.
I've met that girl several times.
She's spoiled.
High-maintenance.
You must have suffered quite a lot.
Let me ask you.
What are you going to do with her?
I'm thinking...
since she's not my wife anymore,
maybe we should send her back to Susha.
You fool!
Her father and brother are dead now.
What can she do back in Susha?
She's like this fan.
On hot summer days,
it's of some use.
But once the weather turns cold,
it becomes useless.
I consider you my own child.
You've been upset.
I'll stand up for you..
What do you think?
Do
as you see fit, Mother.
Xiyang has misplaced her efforts.
Even the Emperor
has been influenced by her.
Don't bother yourself
with matters about her.
Leave them to me.
Also,
there's one more thing
I need to ask you about.
The court of Susha is in chaos now.
This is the perfect timing
to launch an attack.
It's a good opportunity for Jinxiu,
and more so for you.
Would you like to be
a military commander again
and to fight on the battlefield?
I promise
I won't be a disappointment, Mother.
Good.
Mr. Gao!
I am very concerned
about your health.
When you conquer Susha,
I'll find
a good physician for you.
Thank you, Mother.
[IIIII]
Those lines were carved by Huang.
Lady An,
what brings you here?
This morning, Ling Feng came to see me.
That old man
made a bet with me.
He doesn't believe
I can cure Feng Suige's
amnesia.
He said if Feng Suige could
get all the memories back,
he would give me
Zhengnian Villa.
I don't care for his villa.
Ling Feng told me the story
of you and Feng Suige.
Now, I'm just seeking a cure
for Feng Suige,
and also for your sake.
I wish for you two
to spend the rest
of your lives together.
Thank you, Lady An.
In the past, every time I came here,
Huang would be sticking around the tree.
He's also an unfortunate man.
Lord Ling told me
that you saved
Huang's life too.
I did save his life,
but he forgot everything.
He can't remember
about himself and his wife.
He has a wife?
How come I've never seen her?
Huang always sits here alone,
all by himself.
His wife passed away.
When she was gathering herbs for Huang
in the mountain,
a venomous snake bit her.
By the time someone found her,
she had died.
She took this very path to the mountain.
After her passing,
Huang would come and spend time
under this tree every day,
[IIIII]
rain or shine.
Nobody knows why.
[IIIII]
Does he...
keep track of time with these lines?
[IIIII]
You're right.
There are about 60 groups of such lines,
totalling over 300 strokes.
If I remember correctly,
his wife died 10 months ago.
That was about 300 days.
It means
Huang carves a line each day,
to mark
how long it has been since his wife left.
Huang hasn't forgotten her.
He always remembers his wife.
He lingers here every day
in the hope of seeing
his wife come back.
[IIIII]
Right.
Love is deeply engraved in one's heart.
Love can't be
easily forgotten.
Lady An,
I don't believe
Feng Suige would
easily forget about me.
I must still have a place
in his heart.
I firmly
believe he remembers me.
I don't have to
disappear from his life.
There must be other ways
to remind him of me.
Let me think about it.
[Liu Xinglan]
[Shen Wu] [Wang Lang]
This contains the information
of all the civil and military officials
of Susha.
[Diligence and Care for the People]
The Empress Dowager asked me
to carefully study this document,
and to decide which of these officials
are worth establishing ties with.
After all, I've just ascended the throne.
My rule has not been consolidated yet.
I need the assistance of loyal officials.
What's your opinion, Minister Shen?
Your Majesty is
absolutely
correct.
Then who do you think
I should bond with?
-I lack the wit to...
-I'll pick you then.
What do you think?
I...
[Diligence and Care for the People]
thank Your Majesty
for giving me this honor.
Not so quick.
Aren't you curious
why I chose you?
This humble servant
implores Your Majesty
to enlighten him.
After spending over a decade
working in the court,
you've become an expert in politics.
You're also good at
flattering and pleasing others.
You should have held great power
and become a key official of Susha.
But you have a particular habit—
you only curry favor
with those who are influential
without truly submitting yourself
or pledging loyalty
to them.
That's why though you can't be
anyone's trusted confidant,
you can still live a comfortable life.
Even when the Zhuang family fell,
and many were implicated,
you managed to stay out and unscathed.
I'm so sorry.
Alright.
I'm giving you a chance
to work as my confidant.
Are you onboard?
But I've already been
Your Majesty's confidant this entire time.
Everything I have belongs to Susha
and was given by Your Majesty.
I'm showing much sincerity here.
Stop patronizing me,
Minister Shen,
or I'll make you retire.
I'm glad to be Your Majesty's confidant
and loyal servant till my last breath.
Good.
The first task I assign you
is to find out
the cause of death of the late Emperor.
But, Your Majesty,
it's been made clear
that the late Emperor
was murdered by the First Prince.
It is known to all.
I'm asking for the truth.
You're recovering well.
Fortunately, you're strong enough
to survive such severe injuries.
Elder Zhou, Lu Ke told me
that you went to great lengths
to save my life.
I'll never forget
this tremendous favor.
Not at all.
Zhou,
have you figured out a way
to cure his amnesia?
No medicine will work.
At the moment,
I can't think of a solution.
All of you, get out.
I'm telling you to get out.
This matter only concerns him and me.
Your Highness...
Leave the room.
Keep calm, Your Highness.
Lu Ke told me you had left.
Why did you suddenly go away?
Because...
I didn't want to hurt you.
Then why did you come back?
Because...
I missed you.
Back off!
I heard from Lu Ke and Ling Feng
that I had forgotten many things.
They said
you were the love of my life.
I am.
But nothing they say
can erase the memory
of you shooting an arrow at me.
How am I supposed to believe
all of this is true?
Feng Suige, you know what?
I used to deeply regret
shooting that arrow at you
and nearly ending your life.
But now I'm feeling grateful.
I'm grateful for that arrow attack,
since it makes you remember me.
Of course I remember you.
You were the Red-Clad General of Jinxiu,
Fu Yixiao.
Yes.
You were my sworn enemy.
We fiercely fought against
each other on the battlefield,
resorting to every means
to take each other's life.
Yes.
Then how do you explain this?
How did you become the love of my life?
It can't be explained.
And it needs no explanation.
We simply fell in love.
There was no reason for that.
But I don't recall.
It has just temporarily slipped your mind.
Feng Suige,
do you really want to kill me?
♪ The rain drifts endlessly ♪
You hesitated.
♪ The old dream burns the heart ♪
There's already an answer in your heart.
♪ Dreams sink into ruin ♪
You just wouldn't say it out.
♪ Missing the warmth of your palm ♪
Right?
♪ Awaiting dusk ♪
Don't ever think
I won't kill you.
♪ Shadows take root in the mountain pass ♪
♪ In just a moment, tears stained ♪
What are you doing?
Feng Suige,
♪ The world is vast and far ♪
I've promised
to never leave you,
no matter what may happen.
♪ Time is unbearable to endure ♪
If you want me dead,
♪ Lost in the wilderness ♪
I'll forsake my life.
♪ I've been looking for you ♪
♪ Even if devastation fills my eyes ♪
♪ The shadows continue to sway ♪