[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 29]
How long do you plan to keep me locked up?
What do you want to do when you get out?
Go back to Susha to find your father?
I've already divorced Xia Jingshi.
Your Majesty, please send a message
to inform my father and brother that
the marriage alliance between
our two kingdoms has been annulled
and that I will return home soon.
This time,
I truly want to help you.
But I really can't.
Right.
Why would I expect you to help me?
You're the one who
imprisoned me here.
It's not that I don't want to help you.
I just can't
deliver messages to the dead.
What did you say?
You heard me correctly.
Your father and your brother
are both dead.
Your father and brother are dead!
My father died long ago.
And I wish my brother
would die sooner!
Xia Jingyan.
If you have nothing to say,
then don't speak.
If you keep talking nonsense,
don't blame me for being rude to you.
I knew you wouldn't believe me.
This is an urgent report
from our spy in Susha.
Take a look for yourself.
[Prime Minister Zhuang Shen of Susha
has died. The First Prince, Feng Suige,]
[tried to kill the emperor
and seize the throne.]
[Feng Pingcheng,
the Emperor of Susha Kingdom, is dead.]
[Feng Suige was executed.]
It's fake, right?
Xia Jingyan,
to mess with me,
you actually wrote something like this
to scare me?
If I'd known this could really
scare you,
I would've done it long ago.
Why didn't I think of this before?
Do you believe it now?
No.
Looks like you do.
♪ Flying alone ♪
Move!
No need to chase her.
♪ With no need for direction ♪
I'm going back!
I'm going back to Susha!
♪ Flying up to the clouds ♪
♪ Yet the sun is hiding ♪
None of you can fool me.
My father and brother are fine.
♪ Roaming freely ♪
None of you can deceive me.
♪ Unafraid of wind or frost ♪
♪ The wet wings ♪
♪ Will carry me far away ♪
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
I'm going back to Susha!
I'm going home!
♪ I'll remember the way home ♪
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
♪ I'll find the way home ♪
Going back to Susha?
So what if you go back?
Is there still a place for you
in Susha?
Your father is already dead.
And your brother is
a criminal who killed the emperor
and usurped the throne.
You don't want to hear it?
That just makes me
want to say it even more.
You chose to betray Susha
in the first place.
You chose to save Xia Jingshi.
Anyone who gets involved with Xia Jingshi
never ends well.
He deserves to die.
And you—for being heartbroken over him—
you deserve it even more.
Feng Xiyang,
you have no home anymore.
You have no family left.
You're just a wandering ghost
with nowhere to belong.
This is
your punishment for marrying Xia Jingshi.
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
♪ I'll remember the way home ♪
Remember.
Remember the taste of these tears.
That's the taste of your punishment.
Never forget it for the rest of your life.
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
♪ I'll find the way home ♪
Look!
There's one more person in this world
who hates Xia Jingshi!
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
♪ I'll remember the way home ♪
Mention my father and my brother again
and see what happens!
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
Take her back to the Mirror Room!
♪ I'll find the way home ♪
Yes!
Let go of me!
♪ I'll find the way home ♪
Is Feng Pingcheng really dead?
Yes.
The news has spread throughout the palace.
I secretly looked into it.
Feng Suige killed his father
and emperor.
Feng Pingcheng died on the spot,
and Feng Suige
was executed by the Murong family.
Impossible.
From what I know of Feng Suige,
he would never commit
patricide.
Who is currently
ruling Susha?
Murong Zhong and his son.
That explains everything.
I bet
Feng Suige and Feng Pingcheng
were both killed
by the Murong Zhong and his son,
and Feng Suige was then framed
for patricide.
What about Yixiao?
Is there any news of her?
Not yet.
Keep sending people to look.
As soon as there's any news,
come back and inform me immediately.
Yes.
Susha is now in such great turmoil.
It's busy dealing with its own mess.
They won't start a war anytime soon.
Which means,
with the borders stable,
the Empress Dowager and her son
have no more use for me.
Your Highness, are you saying...
Xia Jingyan will do everything
to get rid of me.
We need to speed up our plan.
How's the task
I gave Bai Shouzhuo going?
Everyone you asked for has been contacted.
They're waiting for your command.
Tonight,
I'll meet with our people
myself
and plan the next step.
We'll be there once we cross this river.
How do we get across?
Swim?
There's a boat over there.
Let's go.
Nobody move!
We're on the same side.
We know people from the Storm Alliance.
[Zhang Dongshi,
Elder of Fishing Branch, Storm Alliance]
Who exactly are you?
How did you find this place?
Girl,
it's me!
[Wufeng Mountain, Storm Alliance]
Ning Fei,
have some water and rest.
Ning Fei.
[Shennong's Materia Medica]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
You should stop caring about me.
Ning Fei,
I came to the Storm Alliance
specifically to find you.
Although your physical wounds have healed,
your emotional wounds haven't.
No matter what,
I need to
heal you completely.
Elder Zhou.
You saved Ning Fei's life.
But he's been
[Shennong's Materia Medica]
so melancholy. How can that be?
Could you please help me talk to him?
[Shennong's Materia Medica]
[Zhou Hao,
Elder of Studying Branch, Storm Alliance]
Heaven, earth, and all things
are the same.
Whether he should feel joy or sorrow
should not be forced.
Just let him follow his heart.
Elder Zhou,
Lord Ling brought a patient here.
The situation is serious.
He's been placed in the treatment room.
Alright, I'll go take a look.
Elder Feng,
are my father and the others here?
Yes.
He's in the treatment room.
Ning Fei,
my father is here.
Come.
I'll take you to meet
the person who saved your life.
Let's go.
Lord Ling,
you said he wouldn't last five days.
How is he now?
Don't worry.
Elder Zhou of the Storm Alliance
practices medicine differently from me.
His methods are unorthodox.
He'll surely find a way to save him.
Father!
Sister.
Elder Zhou, the patient is here.
Alright, let me take a look.
Yixiao?
Ning Fei.
Feng Suige?
He is Feng Suige?
He's Feng Pingcheng's son, right?
Girl.
-I'll kill him!
-Girl!
Calm down.
Let me explain.
Let me explain!
[Storm Alliance]
Why did you stop me
from killing Feng Suige?
For such a serious matter,
we should wait for Elder Lei's approval.
I brought him here.
If you don't save him,
[Lei Lie, Elder of Woodcutting Branch,
Storm Alliance]
I must take him away.
Don't waste your words.
Lord Ling,
I understand
everything you said.
Since you understand,
will you save him or not?
Why did you ask
when you already know the answer?
Back then, Feng Pingcheng sent troops
to wipe out the Storm Alliance.
We suffered heavy casualties.
The Storm Alliance and the Feng family
are sworn enemies.
Bringing a Feng descendant
to the Storm Alliance
is asking for death.
But don't forget,
Feng Suige is also
Wei Qingyu's son.
But he still bears the Feng name!
Anyone from the Feng family
is our Storm Alliance's
mortal enemy.
Elders,
what do you think?
I'll listen to my godfather.
I'm a doctor.
I don't want to stand by
and let someone die.
Why don't you
make the decision yourselves?
Rules are rules.
Fine.
Today we'll follow the rules.
The Fengs are our enemies.
I'll kill Feng Suige for revenge!
Storm Alliance was founded
[Great Shelter Hall]
by Feng Suige's mother.
Everyone in the Alliance
has benefited from her kindness.
The current four elders are led
by Lei Lie from the Woodcutting Branch.
And Elder Lei hates the Fengs most.
But for my father's sake,
they shouldn't make things too hard
for Feng Suige.
Lord Ling once told me
never to reveal his identity.
I'm afraid
he can't resolve this matter either.
I'll go in and take a look.
[Great Shelter Hall]
Ning Fei.
You can't go.
You're now a member of the Storm Alliance.
You can't openly help Yixiao.
[Great Shelter Hall]
Stop!
Get out of my way.
I failed Yixiao.
If you kill him,
after you die,
how will you face Qingyu?
You can't enter!
You cannot go in!
Feng Suige's mother
once showed kindness to all of you.
Now her son's life is hanging by a thread.
Not only do you refuse to save him,
but you also want to kill him.
Isn't this
repaying kindness with betrayal?
Years ago, Feng Pingcheng
killed Qingyu despite their marriage bond,
then sent troops
to wipe out our Storm Alliance.
That blood debt
falls on Feng Suige.
A son paying for his father's sins
is only natural.
You probably don't know
the full truth.
Feng Suige's mother
was killed by Susha's Prime Minister,
Zhuang Shen.
How do you know this?
I heard it with my own ears,
witnessed it with my own eyes,
and personally helped Feng Suige
capture Zhuang Shen.
Everyone in Susha knows
that the First Prince Feng Suige
executed Zhuang Shen
and cleared his mother's name.
Feng Suige avenged his mother.
And you elders
of the Storm Alliance—
not only did you do nothing,
you didn't even figure out
who your true enemy was.
Regardless,
he is still Feng Pingcheng's son.
He has the Feng family blood
flowing in his veins.
Are you sure
it was Feng Pingcheng who ordered
the attack on the Storm Alliance?
I heard him myself say
he never took your Storm Alliance
seriously.
If he had truly decided
to wipe out the Storm Alliance
and sent his army,
none of you would be alive today.
Tell me—
Feng Suige's mother
was killed by Zhuang Shen,
so who is it
that fears your secret revenge
and wants to wipe out
the Storm Alliance completely?
Nonsense!
You're just making up lies
to save Feng Suige!
Enough. Stop arguing.
Allow me a moment
to weigh whether this is true.
Keep Feng Suige under guard for now.
Elder Lei,
you cannot be soft-hearted.
Since Big Brother said so,
let's think it over
before making a decision.
I'll make this clear:
if you want to kill Suige,
you'll have to kill me first.
I'll go check on him.
Zhou Hao!
If you dare try
to save Feng Suige,
don't blame me for being harsh with you.
[Storm Alliance]
How is he?
Is there any way to treat him?
I'm just here to check on him.
Those three elders haven't agreed,
so I can't treat him.
Sifang Elixir?
Zhou, what are you...
Keep quiet.
Feng Suige's condition doesn't look good.
Put this under his tongue.
It will help him hold on
for a few more days.
Hurry.
Thank you, Elder Zhou.
Elder Zhou,
can you find any way
to make an exception?
I'll do anything
as long as you can save him.
I want to save him too.
I'm alone
and none of my family
died in that siege,
but Elder Lei
and Elder Zhang
watched
their children
die in that siege.
Their hatred of the Feng family
runs too deep.
Reconciling that hatred
will be extremely difficult.
Zhou.
I'll go to your place
to get some medicine.
Help me out.
Sister.
Although Ning Fei didn't say it,
I know in his heart
he must feel very guilty.
What happened to him?
He seems like
a completely different person.
It was Elder Zhou
who saved Ning Fei back then.
When he woke up,
he even asked why he bothered saving him,
saying it would've been better
to let him die.
Later, Elder Feng
took him into the Farming Branch.
Every day, apart from working the fields,
he just sits in a daze,
hardly speaking a word.
He believes that
since his brothers,
his Jinxiu,
his prince,
and everything he believed in
and stood for
are all gone,
he might as well be dead.
Once Feng Suige
pulls through this ordeal,
I'll try to talk some sense into him.
Alright.
[Cuiwei Palace]
Greetings, Your Eminence.
When I received your secret message,
I gathered them here
to await your arrival.
[Xunzi]
[The palace lantern appeared.
Let's meet up at Cuiwei Palace]
[Xunzi]
[The palace lantern appeared.
Let's meet up at Cuiwei Palace]
You've been hiding in the palace
for so many years.
You've all suffered greatly.
Heaven shows no mercy,
and darkness draws near.
Only you
can save all living beings.
The moment we heard of your return,
we've been ready
to meet you at any time.
Your Eminence,
is our great cause
about to begin?
Are you all ready?
Just give the order,
and we will give our lives
without hesitation.
What if I order you
to kill the Emperor, Xia Jingyan?
What?
Are you afraid?
Your Eminence, for you,
we would die without hesitation.
♪ Flying alone ♪
♪ With no need for direction ♪
♪ Flying up to the clouds ♪
On the wedding day,
♪ Yet the sun is hiding ♪
I'll wear the ones
my father bestowed upon me.
Not because
they're priceless,
♪ Roaming freely ♪
but because
they carry his love—
♪ Unafraid of wind or frost ♪
that's what makes them truly precious.
♪ The wet wings ♪
♪ Will carry me far away ♪
Don't come over!
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
Xiyang!
Put down the knife!
Leave!
Or I swear I'll die right here!
♪ I'll remember the way home ♪
There's no turning back from here.
If you want to stay,
get off the carriage now.
There's no turning back for me now.
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
Wherever you go,
that's where I'll be.
♪ I'll find the way home ♪
Don't cry.
Don't cry!
You are the daughter
of Susha's founding emperor,
Feng Pingcheng.
You are the sister
of the Killer God of Susha,
Feng Suige.
You are the last bloodline
of the Feng family.
♪ Don't cry, don't cry ♪
You must not fall here.
You must avenge them.
♪ I'll find the way home ♪
Girl.
Go back and rest.
You mustn't exhaust yourself.
I'm fine.
I can hold on.
Right now,
I just want to find a way
to get the elders
of the Storm Alliance to agree to save him
as quickly as possible.
Lord Ling,
you must know about
the situation
of the Storm Alliance, right?
Please tell me about it.
Feng Suige has never
told me about it.
When his mother founded
the Storm Alliance, he was still young.
He doesn't know much about many things.
Back then,
Qingyu was helping Feng Pingcheng
fight for power.
Once she was seriously injured.
Feng Pingcheng
brought her to Zhengnian Villa,
asking me to save her.
But before she fully recovered,
Feng Pingcheng rushed back
to the battlefield.
I spared no effort
and finally saved Qingyu.
I remember after she woke up,
she told me
she felt like she had died once,
and that many of the things
she had once clung to
no longer mattered.
I feel as if I have died once.
Only after walking through hell
did I truly understand
how precious life is.
I can understand that feeling.
When I fell off the cliff,
it felt like I had died once too.
You and Qingyu
are both brave and resourceful heroines,
with great abilities
but not arrogant.
And both of you are compassionate.
After Qingyu recovered,
she grew weary of war
and stayed at Zhengnian Villa to help.
And in doing so,
she saw much of the suffering
caused by war.
Mom!
Zhengnian Villa
has its own rules.
The wounded I take in
are treated regardless of faction,
and no fighting is allowed.
So enemies who were killing each other
on the battlefield yesterday
must live
peacefully
in my villa today.
The warriors fight
because they have no choice.
No one likes war,
and no one
wants to suffer from war.
If they can coexist peacefully,
why wouldn't they?
That was
when Chief Wei
had the idea
to establish the Storm Alliance?
That's right.
Qingyu realized that the warring sides
could reconcile.
She told me
that although she couldn't stop the war
single-handedly,
at the very least she could treat
the wounded and displaced,
giving them a chance to survive.
So the Storm Alliance
was meant to be a utopia,
where people could fish, farm, work,
and study in peace.
Exactly.
But since Qingyu was gone,
what has the Storm Alliance become?
It's become filled with hatred—
hatred toward the Feng family
and Susha.
[Storm Alliance]
I feel as if I have died once.
Only after walking through hell
did I truly understand
how precious life is.
[Storm Alliance]
With dark skies and stormy weather,
the roosters keep on crowing.
This place should be called
the Storm Alliance.
[Storm Alliance]
Greetings, Elder Lei.
I'm sorry for disturbing you
with my late-night visit.
You're here to plead for Feng Suige?
You want to say
that what happened back then
had nothing to do with the Fengs
and to persuade me to let go of my grudge?
Feng Suige didn't do anything wrong.
He didn't choose
to be the son of Feng Pingcheng.
This is his fate.
My two sons
both died in the siege back then.
What did they do wrong?
Do the grudges of the previous generation
really have to make
this generation
bear the full burden?
I know exactly what kind of person
Feng Pingcheng is.
Not a single person in the Feng family
is decent.
Feng Suige is different from his father.
If he were truly like Feng Pingcheng,
obsessed with power,
he would have already become
the emperor of Susha by now.
He has never harmed
any innocent person.
He shouldn't have to
unjustly pay
for faults that aren't his.
I don't care what kind of person he is.
I only know
he is my enemy.
[Storm Alliance]
Elder Lei,
why was
the Storm Alliance founded
in the first place?
Why was it called the Storm Alliance?
What was its original purpose?
What are you trying to say?
I brought Feng Suige here back then
because I held hope in my heart.
I didn't know
what kind of place this was.
I only heard
the name Storm Alliance,
heard that there might be a chance
to save Feng Suige,
and came without hesitation.
Shouldn't this
be a paradise
that shelters all and protects people
from the storm?
From now on,
this will be a place that shelters all
and protects people from the storm.
I heard that back then, Chief Wei
founded the Storm Alliance
to give those who were displaced,
who could see
no hope of survival,
a place to settle again,
a place where they could live
and work in peace
in chaotic times.
Although I've never met her,
I admire her.
Throughout my life,
I've also experienced many hardships.
It's precisely because
I've been caught in the rain
that I can't bear to watch others
struggle helplessly in the storm.
If I have the ability
to save someone in danger,
I will do everything in my power to help.
If Feng Suige's mother
were still alive,
I believe
she would do the same.
Those who bring warmth to others
must not be left to freeze in the snow.
Feng Suige's mother
saved so many people
through the Storm Alliance.
Her son
shouldn't have
to lose his chance to live like this.
I believe
the original purpose
of founding the Storm Alliance
was to let those
suffering in the cold and hunger
see light in the darkness—
to give the homeless people
hope
and to help them survive.
Without her,
many of us
wouldn't be alive today.
So...
are you saying you're willing to save
Feng Suige?
Mention my father and my brother again
and see what happens!
Your Majesty.
Do you want to die?
Get out!
All of you, get out!
Stop right there!
How dare you barge into Shengfu Palace?
Who's causing trouble here?
Your Majesty,
the Princess of Zhennan
is trying to force her way in.
Outrageous!
Let her in.
[Shengfu Hall]
Princess of Zhennan
barging into Shengfu Palace?
How dare you?
I've already told you—
I've divorced Xia Jingshi.
I'm no longer Princess of Zhennan.
Don't ever call me that again.
Did you really divorce Xia Jingshi?
Bai Shouzhuo.
My useless brother
was really abandoned?
Good!
This family disgrace
must be spread far and wide.
Got it?
Yes.
Ask him to leave us.
I have something to tell you.
Get out.
You want to ask me for something?
Let me guess.
You want me to show mercy
and let you return to Susha again?
That's not the attitude
of someone asking for a favor.
You should at least kneel down
and kowtow to me.
Interesting.
This is the first time
I've seen someone ask for favors
like this.
If you kill me,
you won't survive either.
You said that I'm a homeless,
wandering ghost.
Since I have no one left
to care about in this world,
why should I fear death?
Both my father and brother
wanted to kill you when they were alive.
Why don't I kill you
to comfort
their spirits in heaven?
Are you so eager
to go join your father
and brother?
I already know
what it feels like to be slapped.
I don't like it.
It hurts!
Remember this feeling too.
This is your retribution
for humiliating me!
What a vengeful
Princess of Susha.
You're more interesting than I thought.
My brother
would never murder our father and emperor.
Someone killed them.
Find the killer who murdered
my father and brother!
Are you ordering me?
Who do you think you are?
Didn't anyone teach you
that when you ask for help,
you must pay a price?
That's what fairness means.
I can help you.
But what can you offer me?
As long as you help me,
I'll promise you anything.
What?
Servants!
Your Majesty.
Investigate
how Feng Pingcheng died.
Within three days,
you must uncover the truth.
If you fail,
I'll kill you all.
Yes.
Where have you been?
[Yujian Pavilion]
I'm asking you,
Princess Xiyang.
What does it have to do with you?
I've already divorced you.
The bond between us as husband and wife
no longer exists.
My affairs have nothing to do with you.
Princess Xiyang.
If you dare bother me again,
I swear I'll kill you.
[Yujian Pavilion]
Forgive me.
You must've heard about
what happened in Yujing City, haven't you?
You're here to kick me when I'm down?
I'm just worried about you.
Is there anything I can do to help you?
Spare me
your fake concern.
You're not even worth my curses.
Princess Xiyang,
if you need
any help from me,
feel free to ask.
Though
we are no longer
husband and wife,
we're still acquaintances.
I mean no harm.
I only wish to help.
Acquaintances?
Do I really know you?
Why is it that
the longer we were together,
the more of a stranger you became?
You're not
the Prince of Zhennan
I once fell in love with.
We never truly knew each other.
Besides,
the Feng Xiyang you know
is already dead.
[Yujian Pavilion]
♪ Flying alone ♪
♪ With no need for direction ♪
♪ Flying up to the clouds ♪
♪ Yet the sun is hiding ♪
♪ Roaming freely ♪
♪ Unafraid of wind or frost ♪
♪ The wet wings ♪
♪ Will carry me far away ♪
[Yujian Pavilion]
♪ I'll find the way home ♪
I've treated his external wounds.
They're not serious.
The biggest problem now
is the blockage of his blood and qi.
We can only try to stimulate
his heart meridian
and see if it helps him
regain consciousness.
But I've already used acupuncture
to stimulate his heart meridian.
There was no improvement.
Ordinary acupuncture won't work anymore.
Look at his blood flow—
it's like a frozen river,
completely blocked.
Come on.
Pierce his finger to release blood
and help his energy circulate.
I'll handle
the rest.
Alright.
Let me see
your extraordinary acupuncture technique.
Good.
He's responding.
Pierce his Shaoshang point.
He moved.
Press his Zuzhong point.
I'll press on his upper body.
Let's get his breath back.
Come on.
[Treatment Room]
Elder Zhou,
Lord Ling.
How is...
Feng Suige?
He's not awake yet,
but his life's no longer in danger.
That brat Feng Suige won't die.
He's been unconscious for too long.
We'll have to wait until
he wakes up to know
his exact condition.
No words can express my gratitude.
[Treatment Room]
Thank you, Elder Zhou.
Thank you. You two are saints.
Thank you.
[Fuxin Pavilion]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, why did you summon me?
I heard that
you dissolved your marriage
with Prince of Zhennan without permission.
That's right.
This marriage
concerns the politics of both our nations—
it's not just a personal matter
between you two.
You made such a decision
without consulting me.
Do you still respect my authority?
The politics of two nations?
At this point,
does that still matter?
I've heard about what happened
to your father and brother.
The dead are gone.
My condolences.
Take care of yourself.
When your brother
Feng Chengyang ascends the throne,
you'll become the Grand Princess of Susha,
representing Susha's image abroad.
It seems to you,
who I am doesn't matter,
nor does whether Prince of Zhennan
and I get along.
What matters is my status.
You're a smart woman.
I like talking to smart people.
Your sudden misfortune
made you lose your bearings,
so I'll overlook your rashness.
Go back, show humility, and apologize
to Prince of Zhennan.
You'll still be Princess of Zhennan.
As long as you obey,
I'm willing to be your protector.
If I'm not mistaken,
that's how you
took advantage
of Xia Jingshi's weakness back then
and gradually
brought him under your control, isn't it?
He's a man who knows how to adapt.
I hope you are too.
Then I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
I've always
made a habit
of taking control of my own fate.
Marrying Xia Jingshi
was my decision.
Taking Xia Jingshi away from Susha
Divorcing him
was also my decision.
Since I've decided
to cut all ties with him,
even if it costs me my life,
I'll never change my mind.
I gave you a chance,
but you refused it.
Don't regret it later.
Thank you for your kindness, Your Majesty.
However,
aside from my father and brother,
I need no one's protection.
I, Feng Xiyang,
am my own protector.